fictionpress.com 2019-12-16

# Privacy Policy | FictionPress

**FictionPress.com Privacy Policy**

The FictionPress.com Privacy Policy describes how FictionPress.com treat personal information when you use FictionPress.com services. 

**Data collection**

  * FictionPress.com may collect information about the device (which includes web browsers, mobile phones, computers or other internet connected devices) you use to access FictionPress.com services. This log information may include but not limited to your internet protocol address, device info, date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your device. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services. 
  * Some of our services require you to register for an account and provide some personal information (typically a user name, email address and password). 

**Cookies/Unique Identifiers**

  * Please visit our Cookies Policy page for details. 

**Information sharing**

We do not share your personal information with companies, organizations, or individuals outside of outside of FictionPress.com except for the following cases: 

  * We have your consent. 
  * For external processing: We may provide personal information to affiliates and other trusted businesses or persons to process it for us, based on our instructions and in compliance with our Privacy Policy. For example, we use service providers to help with customer support. 
  * For legal reasons: We may provide personal information when we have a good-faith believe that access, use, preservation, or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 
    * Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request.
    * Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
    * Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues.
    * Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of FictionPress.com, our users, or the public as required or permitted by law. 

**Information security**

  * We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. 
  * When applicable, we use industry standard encryption to protect the communication between all compatible devices and our services. 
  * We restrict access to your personally identifying information to site staffs who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. 

**Updating your information**

  * We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for many of our services. For more information, please see the help pages for each service. 

**Third-party Advertisers, Technology Partners, External Links**

FictionPress.com allows other companies, called third-party ad networks, to serve advertisements within FictionPress.com. These third-party ad networks use technology to send, directly to your device, the advertisements and links that appear on FictionPress.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. 

FictionPress.com allows other companies, called Technology Partners, to to provide analytics or other contracted work to augment the FictionPress.com service. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad networks and technology partners for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Any data obtained by third-party ad networks or technology partners subsequently shared with FictionPress.com is maintained and dealt with by FictionPress.com in accordance with this privacy policy. 

FictionPress.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, external web sites/services. For example, links to external websites/services not affiliated with FictionPress.com. 

Please refer to the privacy policy of our technology partners

  * Google: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

**Last Updated Feb 12, 2019**
